▍2026 美网 男单1/4决赛
蒂亚福 5-7 3-6 7-5 6-3 7-6⁶ 米切尔森 · 赛后场上采访
Frances, let's go back over two hours ago.
弗朗西斯，两个多小时前
You're down two sets to love.
你当时两盘落后
Alex serving for the match.
亚历克斯的发球胜赛局
What do you tell yourself in that moment
那一刻你会怎么提醒自己
when you're going back to return?
准备走回去接发球时
I hope he gets tight.
我希望他紧张起来
And, you know,
然后，你知道
just play a super tough game.
尽力打好这艰难的一局
Obviously, you know,
显然，你知道
he gave me some gifts with a couple
他送了我些机会，几个
of double faults there.
双误帮了忙
And then I slowly,
然后我慢慢
slowly started to get my rhythm there,
慢慢地找到自己的节奏
snuck out that third set,
艰难拿下了第三盘
and only started playing better and better.
接着越打越好
But he's a hell of a player, man.
但他真是个厉害的球员
I mean, he easily should have won today.
他今天本来很有希望赢
So shout out to Alex Michelsen.
向亚历克斯·米切尔森致敬
In matches like
像这样
this, these are iconic matches, seven, six,
这样的经典比赛，七比六
in the fifth.
而且是在决胜盘
How important is it for this crowd
现场观众
to get behind you in those big moments?
在关键时刻支持有多重要
Yeah, everyone was sleeping
是啊，大家都像睡着了
the first couple of hours.
刚开始的那几个小时
I was like, what's going on?
我当时想，怎么回事
I was asleep with y'all.
我也跟你们一起睡着了
And then as it went along,
后来随着比赛进行
the energy was incredible as it is always.
现场能量一如既往地惊人
Thank you, obviously, two Americans,
谢谢，虽然都是美国球员
but you guys are really for me,
但你们特别支持我
and I really appreciate that.
我真的很感激
And finally, you're into the semifinals
最后，你打进了半决赛
for your third time.
这是第三次了
Tonight, Carlos Alcaraz plays Ben Shelton.
今晚阿尔卡拉斯对阵谢尔顿
You play the winner of that match.
你将对阵他们中的胜者
Are you going to be locked in watching
今晚你会专心看
that match tonight?
那场比赛吗
Let your team watch it.
还是让团队去看
You're going to chill.
你自己放松一下
What's the game plan? Well, hence,
有何安排？——嗯，毕竟
they've got to play right now.
他们马上就要打了
I've already, I played for four hours forty.
我已打了四小时四十分钟
But for sure, I'll watch,
不过我肯定会看
but I'm going to enjoy this one, though.
但我要先享受这场胜利
Let's go!
来吧！